herzing.edu 2019-06-19

# Herzing University Policy Statement

### General Information

Herzing University has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our Institution's commitment to privacy and the protection of personal information. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: herzing.edu.

### Our Privacy Pledge

Herzing University will use your personal information for the purposes of enhancing your experience with our site and your investigation of an education with our institution. As well as to answer any questions you may have concerning our campuses and programs. We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. We may from time to time use your email or other contact information provided herein, to enhance our ability to attract similar students as you, that might be interested in Herzing University.

Herzing University's inquiry form requests that users provide contact information (such as their name, mailing address, telephone number, and email address). We use this contact information to send the user additional information about our school. A user's contact information may also be used by us to contact the user directly. Users may choose not to receive future mailings or other communications from Herzing University at any time by going to [unsubscribe.herzing.edu](http://unsubscribe.herzing.edu/). 

### Information Regarding Contacting Our Prospective Students by Telephone

Herzing University is in compliance with the FCC’s Amendments to the Telephone Consumer Protection Act which went into effect 10/16/2013. This act protects consumers by regulating the way in which companies can call consumer’s cell phones and send texts to those cell phones. Specifically, consumers must give a company, "prior express consent" (achieved by submitting the information request form) to agree to allow that company to deliver information about their services via text messages, automatically dialed phone messages and/or pre-recorded voice information. While consent must be given to receive information via telephone, consent is not necessary to apply to or be admitted to the university.

This website provides links to sites of other organizations solely as a convenience to our visitors; we do not endorse these organizations nor are we responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, herzing.edu makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/>.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.  
Our advertising partners include Google AdSense.

### Google AdSense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Nitlogic.net sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

Herzing University has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Herzing.edu's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

### Disclaimer

Herzing University's website provides information on many topics. While our staff strives to provide accurate information to our site users, we make no guarantees regarding the accuracy or reliability of this content.

This website provides links to sites of other organizations solely as a convenience to our visitors; we do not endorse these organizations nor are we responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

### Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can E-mail: [webinfo@herzing.edu](mailto:webinfo@herzing.edu).
